Ez egy népszerűtlen lány története...
Egy népszerűtlen lány története...
Lány
Népszerűtlen
Népszerűtlen  Lány
Népszerűtlen Lány
Népszerűtlen lányok?
Nem volt még kapcsolatban
Sosem hívták el randira
Még szűz
A népszerűtlenség jelei
Értem...
Egy vacak történet a mindennapjaiból.
Más szóval, egy ronda lány aki nem kell senkinek.
Ez annyira nem én vagyok.
Elvégre, korábban nem kevesebb mint hatszor beszélgettem fiúkkal!
Milyen óránk lesz most?
Mi? Ő... Angol.
He?
Ha leesett a radirom háromból egyszer mindig fiú vette fel.
Tessék.
Volt, hogy még ők közeledtek felém!
Bocsi, otthonmaradt a könyvem.
Nem is lehetnék népszerűbb!
Ráadásul következő hónaptól,
gimis leszek!
Gimiben csúcsosodhat ki az ember népszerűsége!
Dühöngő hormonok és nemi vágyak az összes fiút hozzám vonza majd, három kerek évig!
Már ötven évet lehúztam randi-szimulátorokban
és már száz különböző fiúval összejöttem.
Alaposan felkészültem mindenre!
Alig várom a napot mikor végre igazi gimnazista leszek!
Május közepe van...
Komolyan!
That's so weird!
Totally!
Furcsa.
Már két hónapja járok ide de még senkivel sem beszéltem.
Miért?
l'm telling you
Another typical day begins
I catch everyone's eyes only too easily
I have some good days because I'm small
I know I'm right
What I felt back then
Will change sometime, you say?
I hate it when you label me
I don't even want to be like you
So you just ignore us
And try to live on your own
That day when someone was kind to me
l tell them to get lost
Get out! Get out! I point at the door
An age without dreams
Has opened my eyes
Will I ever be popular?
The world won't allow that
Even if you're popular you must struggle
There's more work to be done
All resistance is futile
Cheer up! Cheer up!
Get popular! Get popular!
Let's meet in a future where everything's changed
No matter how I look at it
It's you guys' fault that I'm not popular
No Matter How I Look at  It,
It's You Guys' Fault I'm Not Popular!
Lament
Since I'm Not
Popular, I'll Change
My Image a Bit
Lament
Since I'm Not
Popular, I'll Change
My Image a Bit
Mi a fene folyik itt?
Várj, még semmi okom idegeskedni.
Még rengeteg időm van összejönni valakivel.
Emlékeztek amikor karaokézni mentünk?
Kinyomtattam a fényképeket amiket csináltunk!
Semmi ok a pánikra...
Pff, mi van ezzel a képpel?
Pánik...
Fúj, olyan csúnya vagyok ezen a képen.
Pá—
Mit számít? Elvégre van már barátod.
N-Nem vagyok ideges!
Girls who form their own cliques like that are just ditzy sluts anyway!
Only douchebags would hang around bitches like them!
I'd rather be alone than hang out with those pieces of trash.
Well...
Maybe not alone.
I'll just be having fun playing by myself.
I'm not like those whores who wear gaudy make-up and short skirts just to get boys.
Go ahead and live out your clichéd adolescence with your fellow scum.
Viszont látásra tanárúr!
'sztok. Aztán tanuljatok is a vizsgárka ne csak lustálkodjatok.
Rendben!
Tényleg... tanultál már?
Egy mukkot sem!
Ugye? Még én sem!
Közeledik a félévi számonkérés.
Ha jól sikerülnek akkor biztosan...
Kukori te olyan okos vagy.
Ezt magyarázd el.
Hát, tudod...
Sokan fognak hozzám fordulni!
Menjünk.
Kuroki
Hé!
nem jössz el velem tanulni a vendéglőbe?
Jól hangzik.
Mi?
Elmentek párban tanulni?
Van hely még kettőnek?
Micsoda?
Komolyan?
Miért ne?
Can't this school be invaded by terrorists or something?
Cram school blows.
Wanna skip?
That's probably a bad idea.
How about we just meet up after?
Sure.
Or maybe the Shorty Aliens from G**tz could attack,
or Shimada from P***syte could show up.
After he's been doused with sulfuric acid, of course.
Viszont látásra!
Szia. Odafigyelni ám az úton.
Kuroki, figyelj oda az úton.
V'szlát.
Olyan régen nem beszéltem senkivel a suliban, hogy
már köszönni sem tudok a tanároknak.
Tomoko!
Elugrok a boltba.
Kérsz valamit?
Uh, twice-cooked pork.
Oké.
Mindjárt jövök.
Anyuhoz minden további nélkül tudok beszélni.
Hát, azt hiszem mindenki tud beszélni legalább a szüleivel.
Idegen emberekkel való beszélgetés számít csak igazán, főleg fiúkkal.
Vissza kell szereznem a szociális képességeimet ami egyszer már megvolt.
Keserű...
Hé, rég láttalak.
Minden reendben?
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Ne válaszolj.
Mondhatjuk...?
Magányos vagyok.
Pardon, pardon. Én...
Pardon, pardon. Én... Nekem is hiányoztál.
Nekem is hiányoztál.
Ezaz. A tervnek megfelelően halad a beszélgetés.
Már csak...
Rub!
Coming...
I'm coming soon!
Rub!
Évek óta nem néztem meg magam a tükörben.
Téves lett volna az énképem?
Helyes vagyok, igaz?
Vagy mégsem?
Minden esetre ronda nem vagyok...
Úgy van.
A csúnya lányokra nézve lenne sértő engem is annak tartani.
De ha nem vagyok csúf akkor miért nem vagyok kelendő?
Azé' mert alacsony vagyok és nincsenek melleim?
Várjunk, akkor miért nem vagyok kedvelt a kislányokat kergetők körében?
Milyen elbűvölő!
Nem lehetek ennyire elragadó!
Mindenki fel fog ismerni!
These eyes, clouded by stress and disregard for my health...
If I fix up my eyes, I can finally live my fun high school life!
Igen! Ez az!
Trot
These glasses hide the dark circles perfectly!
Well, they're my dad's...
But all that matters is that they make me cute, right?
I'm so good, it's scary.
Become cuter and more charming
More! It's not enough!
I want boys... I want guys to look at me!
Megjöttem.
Isten hozott.
Csapzott
Makulátlan
Csábos póz
Duckface
Makulátlan
Csábos póz
Duckface
Makulátlan
Csábos póz
Duckface
Makulátlan
Csábos póz
Duckface
Makulátlan
Csábos póz
Duckface
Makulátlan
Csábos póz
Duckface
Makulátlan
Csábos póz
Duckface
Makulátlan
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Exposed forehead
Duckface
Csábos póz
Exposed forehead
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Exposed forehead
Duckface
Csábos póz
Exposed forehead
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Exposed forehead
Duckface
Csábos póz
Exposed forehead
Duckface
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Duckface
Csábos póz
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Duckface
Csábos póz
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Duckface
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Duckface
Csábos póz
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Duckface
Csábos póz
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Duckface
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Duckface
Csábos póz
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Duckface
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Duckface
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Duckface
Csábos póz
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Duckface
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Csábos póz
Duckface
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Duckface
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Duckface
Good lord! Who's this freakin' ugly chick?!
Exposed forehead
Szemüveg
Duckface
Csábos póz
Szemüveg
Exposed forehead
Csábos póz
Duckface
Oh, it's just you, Sis...
No Matter How I Look at  It,
It's You Guys' Fault I'm Not Popular!
I guess starting with my appearance was the wrong approach.
I need to get back to the basics and
focus on getting my social skills back.
Hey, wanna talk, lil' bro?
Huh?
What do you want from me?
What're you getting comfortable for?
Why shouldn't I? I'm your sister.
You just shouldn't. Go play in traffic.
Wouldn't you rather me play
Winning Eleven with you instead?
No. Get out.
By the way, didn't you have practice today?
We're off because of exams. Get lost already.
Uh... Let's see...
Don't just dig through my stuff!
Go kill yourself!
Yeah. I should just kill myself.
Hold on a minute...
You just got on my nerves a little...
So... y-you know...
You know, I've been thinking...
My life's difficulty level shot up since I started high school.
I'm pretty sure I'm on hard mode now.
By the time I move on to college and join the work force, I'll be on nightmare mode.
I might as well jump straight to the ending now.
I'm sorry, okay? Chill out.
You wanted me for something, right? What's up?
Talk with me.
Huh? What're you on about?
It's just that I haven't had a conversation with anyone lately.
I can no longer hold a conversation with anyone outside of our family.
What?
I need to get rehabilitated back into society! Talk with me for an hour every day!
Maybe when Hell freezes over.
I don't know what your deal is,
but why can't you just talk with your friends instead?
Do you think I have any?
Everyone's gotta have at least one friend.
Well, I'm not a handsome man that's been the forward on the soccer team since my second year like you.
What's up with the respect all of a sudden?
It's true, right?
Every time you score a goal in a soccer game,
you also score with one of the female managers, right?
What are you talking about?
Anyway...
Are you gonna talk with me or not?
Hurry up and decide.
Should I just kill myself now?
If you were my brother, I'd've punched your face by now.
So for how long?
Until I get a friend—no, a boyfriend.
So you're basically sentencing me to life in prison?
No, I think a month should be enough.
She's surprisingly positive.
So what do you want to talk about?
Am I cute?
You're normal.
How cute is "normal"?
Middle-level cute, upper-middle-level cute, lower-middle level cute?
Or more like... Wait,
what does "normal" mean to you, anyway?
I have to do this every day?
Are you kidding me?
Exams are finally over.
Wanna go somewhere since we got out early?
Early dismissal, huh?
Guess I'll surf the net and play a game or two.
Hey!
We're going out to karaoke.
You girls wanna join?
Yeah!
Shut up, you bitches and whores.
How many times a month do you go to karaoke?
I bet you just...
"Okay! I'm gonna sing AK*!"
...do crap like that, right?
I bet they also do lewd things since the rooms are private!
"Oops, I'm getting some feedback from my mic down there."
Gimme a break!
"My speaker makes awesome sounds..."
Just shut the fuck up!
B-Bye...
Later. Be careful on your way home.
I did it!
I had a totally normal conversation with someone!
I think I'll pick up something sweet on the way home!
Welcome.
Guess I should get something for my brother, too.
I do owe him one, after all.
Ymmuy Stick
Total
Platinum Ratio Pudding
That'll be 256 yen.
Would you like a spoon with that?
Yes...
P-Please...
Okay, I'll put one in the bag.
Okay... th-thanks...
Holy shit! I just talked to a hot guy!
All right...
While I'm on a roll, I'll make a few more detours.
Now that I think about it,
I haven't done this since I've started high school.
I wanna go to places high school girls usually frequent,
but you usually go to those places with friends.
I'll start with something easy
and find a place that even I can enjoy without stressing...
Welcome.
People can read manga for free in here,
so nobody would bat an eye at a solo player.
It's a weekday afternoon.
You people should be at home, doing something more important instead.
A place where everyone's lamer than me isn't so bad.
Sorry! Did you wait long?
You're late.
Sorry. Well, let's go.
I'm sorry. Are you mad?
Nah.
Reading twenty books might've been a little bit too much.
Now time for the real detour!
A high school girl should be able to go into a fast food place alone.
Welcome.
Will you be eating here or to-go?
Y-Yes... E-Eating...
h-here.
May I take your order?
H-Hamburger.
Will that be the sandwich alone?
Y-Yes... And is there water... or...
Pardon?
N-Never mind. It's nothing...
Seems like there're plenty of people here by themselves.
Delicious!
GOBBLE
Have hamburgers always tasted this great?!
I thought these things were just for kids and idiots!
Turns out this is plenty of fun, even alone.
Of course, I'm sure it'd be even more fun with friends or a guy...
But hey, there's still time.
Man, I sang my lungs out.
Hey, did someone go home?
Is there only eight of us now?
Disgusting!
Oh, we can all sit here.
All right!
Lucky us!
I'll sit here.
Th-They're from my class...
On their way home from karaoke?
Shit!
Isn't she from our class?
She's always off by herself.
Poor thing, all alone, even in here.
They're totally gonna talk about me!
Also...
Boy
Tomoko
Girl
They'll notice me if I try going down the stairs.
But if I stay here,
Boy
Tomoko
Girl
anyone going to the restroom will notice me.
The restroom!
I didn't think I'd have to dress like this again.
Now I just have to do something about my face...
Yeah, we had to wait in line for like an hour to eat there.
For real?
We should all go there together sometime.
Yeah!
I'm in!
When should we go?
What's wrong?
Nothing. That girl just now had our school's uniform.
You know her?
Nope. So what were you saying?
I asked when we should go.
All right!
What the hell are you doing?
Why are you just standing there? Keep moving.
R-Right...
What?
Did you see her?
That chick was ugly as sin!
You saw her, right, Tomoki?
No, I wasn't looking...
What a waste!
You don't see someone that ugly every day!
OX Park
Let's just go straight home.
'Kay.
I can't even hold a conversation
I really have no clue why
Am I an idiot?
I'm all alone on the way home
I can't even say goodbye to anyone
Sitting around and waiting won't change anything
That's it!
This is just the beginning!
Everything's so simple online
It's been a while since I last spoke
Even being in the sun or rain won't change anything
That's it!
It's not my fault!
So what if I have nothing to do?
So what if I'm all alone?
If I get serious
I'll definitely be popular!
Mirror, mirror on the wall, do you wanna shatter and fall?
No! Stop! No more!
Mirror, mirror on the wall, you don't have to say it all!
Just pretend you can't hear it
You never reflect my beautiful inner self
That's just in your head, it's all in your head
It's always this unappealing side of me
Face the truth
Tomorrow will be the same as yesterday
I really have no clue why
I'm an idiot
Lament
Since I'm Not
Popular, I'll Meet Up
With an Old Friend
Since I'm Not
Popular, I'll Meet Up
With an Old Friend
Lament
So how long do
you plan on staying in here?
You know, I used to have a friend.
Until middle school, that is.
You don't say?
I think I'll try calling her up.
Go for it.
Yeah. I will.
Just don't do it in here.